<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSE@BAUET</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="overview">"The Department of Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) is one of the three departments of the faculty of Electrical and Electronic Engineering (EEE) of Bangladesh Army University of Engineering and Technology (BAUET). The university is located at Qadirabad Cantonment, Natore. CSE@BAUET administers four year long bachelor\'s program in Computer Science and Engineering (B.Sc Engg. in CSE).\n\nAbout ten full-time faculty members provide a comprehensive program that emphasizes algorithms and theory, advanced computer architecture, computer vision and pattern recognition, data mining and machine learning, distributed systems and cloud computing, operating systems and computer networks, computer security and scientific computing, image processing and artificial intelligence.\n\nThe CSE department\'s many strengths include it\'s high faculty-to-student ratio, state of the art facilities, renowned faculty, strong focus on undergraduate education balanced with leading-edge research, and emphasis on leadership, service and ethics. Faculty and students often collaborate on projects, working side-by-side for a better tomorrow, for example, the university\'s website has been designed and developed by the faculty members and students of the CSE department.\n\nThe department also works collaboratively with other departments such as Physics and Mathematics. In addition to the excellent faculty and quality research opportunities available through the department, there is a real sense of community and teamwork here. Laws, regulations and discipline is given topmost priority as well.\n\nThe CSE department also offers various topics to major in for the undergraduate students. These concentrations provide students interested in those topic areas with a recommended sequence of elective courses. Completion of one of the Concentrations is recorded on the student\'s official transcript at graduation.\n\nAlthough CSE@BAUET is a relatively new department, the students are already performing well on various national events and contests. It can be hoped that they will, in future, lead the computing industry and digital arena of Bangladesh."</string>
    <string name="adinfo">"The Department of CSE enrolls students twice a year through two semesters, fall and summer. The summer semester is from February to July while the fall semester is from August to January. Requirement for appearing in the admission test of BAUET is GPA 8.00 (SSC + HSC) for the faculty of EEE (CSE, EEE, ICE). Students having total GPA of 10 are eligible for direct admission.\n\nPayment Information:\n\nFor CSE and EEE Dept,\nAdmission Fee - BDT 1,00,000/=\nFirst Semester Fee - BDT 1,24,000/=\nPer Semester Fee (next 7 semesters) - BDT 80,000/="</string>
    <string name="dev">"Hello! there, my name is Fahim Faisal, I'm a student of CSE at Bangladesh Army University of Engineering and Technology (BAUET). Currently I am working on web development, android app development, Java and embedded systems. I'm a tech enthusiast and always looking for new things to learn. You can follow me on social media for any queries or updates on my latest work by clicking on the above buttons. Thank you."</string>
    <string name="update">"CSE@BAUET\n\nRelease version: 1.0\nCurrent version: 1.0"</string>
    <string name="update2">"Copyright 2017 Fahim Faisal\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\ndistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\nSee the License for the specific language governing permissions and\nlimitations under the License."</string>

</resources>
